Welcome back.
I think I've managed to un-motion my brain.
It took me a day, okay?
I remember at the very end of last time I had some real issues.
I was just stumbling around with some words.
Let's just go in with this with a fresh mind now and have a look at things.
So, yeah.
Let's go back up here.
The problem was I didn't know where to go next.
I was sort of lost.
Let's go back up to where we were.
We found the labs and we deciphered the whole number system and all that, you know, base 10, all that stuff.
But then things went downhill.
Let's see if we can't rectify it a little bit.
Let's look at this map again.
So, okay, right now I just came from the bottom, right?
I just don't understand why this one is saying out of order or closed.
It's clearly not.
I just took it.
Oh yeah, this was supposed to be refinery.
Wait, mine?
Hold on, which one am I looking at?
That one.
This one, refinery.
Yeah.
That one is pretty much confirmed, right?
And I don't think I understand this map entirely.
Because this is clearly a vertical map, right?
I'm going up to the next level.
So this means this is also higher than this.
And then this goes up again.
And this is higher.
Like higher up vertically.
Refinery, silver, gold, copper.
This is the lab.
Cafeteria, machine, fairy gate.
I just seem to remember the mine being over here somewhere.
Wasn't it close to the lab?
And why is the whatever the mine is not over here on the map?
That's the thing that's confusing me right now.
I need to go back over here and see.
I need to see this lab again.
Oh, and let's see if we can actually figure this out.
So right now we are on this level.
So in order to get to the lab, we just have to keep going this way.
Right?
Oh, but not down here apparently.
It's upstairs.
Oh, the cafeteria has just opened.
I wonder what they're serving today.
Probably meatloaf.
I imagine these people eating meatloaf.
Not sure why, but it's just what I think.
I thought he was running to the cafeteria.
Labs, lab one, lab two, right?
Ah, but then there's also this extra one here.
Lab one, lab two, and then this.
This, I think, is mine.
So it's the little circle with the thing down.
The problem here is though, if I'm over here, then the one on the left can't be a mine, obviously.
So I'm missing something.
It just fits so well though, you know?
Mine, it has the line going up and this thing.
But of course, the bottom part could be different.
Maybe there's a glyph I haven't discovered yet that has the same properties, right?
Oh, wait a minute!
This could actually mean lab three.
Because look, the labs also have a circle going down and this going up.
Maybe there is no mine at all.
Oh, I'm so dumb!
Lab one, lab two, of course, because the number... it has to be lab three.
But we don't know where lab three is.
I couldn't see it.
It's either lab three or mine.
Let me actually go back in here to lab two.
According to this sign, this should lead to either a mine or a lab three.
That's lab two up there.
Wait a minute.
There's also a path over here.
Oh, right.
That's true.
Why is it covered up, though?
Yeah, this could be lab.
Actually, to assume it's a lab makes more sense here.
This is like the lab area.
Oh, maybe this lab was overrun by monsters.
Right?
Monsters fear fire.
Yeah.
That one we got.
Why did I assume this to be a mine anyway?
Oh, wait a minute.
I didn't even see this.
Oh, but I guess I still need fire.
Right.
Yeah, we got to find fire somehow.
That's the next step.
Find fire so we can go into, well, the lab or the mine.
Right.
And what's upstairs?
Now we're just going up on the map to the second level.
Yeah.
You know what?
I'm going to call this one.
I don't know what is.
I don't know what that is.
Let's go upstairs.
There's also the library.
Well, the place that's just called books, which is super weird.
Uh, that's the cafeteria.
No doubt about it.
That one is irrefutable.
OK, this guy is counting barrels.
And currently we are on the second floor.
Let's see the map again.
Right.
Fairygate is up there, apparently.
And this is verticality, right?
So if I go left now...
Or is it?
I don't know.
It's so confusing.
This map is so confusing.
Like that would mean that this this is the library, right?
That would suggest that the fairygate is above the library somewhere up here that I can't get to.
But what is over here?
Isn't that the fairygate, though?
Yeah, this has to be the fairygate.
There's just no other way around it.
And I guess it is technically a little up.
But to me, it's more like this is north and this is more south.
You know, it's so confusing.
That map is combining height, so elevation and directions.
It's super weird.
Do I really not have a word for library in any way?
Also, what am I missing here?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, that's why I was guessing mine, right?
Oh.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I think I just got it.
We're not dealing with refineries.
This is the mine slash refinery.
Gold mine, silver mine.
Oh, that makes so much more sense.
This is probably mine.
Cafeteria.
Lab.
These two are 100% confirmed.
And then mine is pretty much confirmed.
This has to be, well, library.
They wouldn't give us this unless we had all the glyphs, right?
Okay.
Thank the Lord.
Library.
Mine.
Refractory?
I have no idea what that means, but I'm assuming it's cafeteria related.
Okay.
Oh, we still have this one.
Man, what could that be?
So what did I call that one?
Elements combination.
Could be alchemy, actually.
Monster and fear.
Man, what is that?
Create, make.
Caterpillar makes a butterfly.
Nope, it does not make a butterfly.
The thing is, though, I must have the glyph for this at the moment.
I must have it.
Fear and monster.
Machine.
What else could it be?
Close?
It's not greetings.
Open.
Is this somehow fire or heat?
Machine?
The machine of life?
I am so confused by that one.
And I'm still kind of lost because I need to find fire.
Because I know I need to combine it.
Oh, now I'm up here.
Well, now that we know it's a mine, let's try and go to the mines again.
Let's take the elevator.
Let's see the map now.
Silver mine.
Okay, good, good, good.
Copper mine.
Nice.
So all of these places are pretty much confirmed now, except the machine.
Yes.
Okay, let's go down.
I guess that's why I was at the bottom last time.
Because I couldn't find anything else up here.
That's why I went down to, well, the mines.
Okay, now I'm on level one.
In fact, we can go left now and go to the other two mines.
That is not copper, so silver and gold.
Which should be here.
Yeah, this is it.
Gold mine.
I still need an access card.
Where the hell do I get that?
I think the thing I'm struggling most with in this area is just knowing where to go.
I'm kind of stuck.
And this thing.
I need to fill this one up with something.
This was gold mine.
Silver mine.
Why are there two light bulbs on?
Does that mean anything at all?
It's just lights.
I think I needed an access card here as well.
Yeah, look, I need an access card.
Can I can I put the silver on this thing?
Maybe it gets processed into a bar or something.
Oh, are you kidding me?
Okay, there was no prompt for it when I held middle mouse.
Oh my god, look at him.
Why would I do this?
Oh my god, look at that.
They are processing.
Monsters ahead.
Actually, this could mean danger.
Danger or warning.
You know, a classic danger sign.
I could walk across here.
There's a little gap in between this.
Man, I'm just happy I finally figured out a new area to go to.
Go.
Run.
Jesus.
Yeah, this is definitely dangerous.
Go.
Oh, nice.
Not bad.
And go.
Oh, fuck.
Back, back, back.
Wait, what?
Go.
Wait here.
Oh, man.
Go.
Again, would it be funny if there was a cut scene where you get hit by those rocks and you just get fucking blasted by them.
You know, limbs falling everywhere, blood, you're just crushed, the head is split in half, organs coming out, guts everywhere.
It was not fit with the game at all, but it would be funny.
Okay, what do we have here?
Oh, this is the thing from the drawing.
First, we open it until something.
I forgot the order.
Okay, now we put in silver.
And I think we do.
Yeah, until it's in that.
Go.
Yes, we're making an ingot.
I call that so early.
Very nice.
Yay.
There it is.
Look at that.
So pretty.
Doesn't look like silver at all.
Okay, in this angle, it does.
In this angle, it doesn't.
It's a little bit funny with the colors.
Okay, we got new stuff.
This has to be water or pipe.
Death.
Oh, open, close.
Open, close, and then this one.
Danger warning.
Yeah, come on.
Okay, death or dead.
I like that they just have a sign that says death.
Yeah, don't go this way or you'll die.
Man, what could that be then?
I mean, I don't know.
We don't have any options here, really.
What does this even mean?
So hold on.
Nature.
Uh, yeah, nature, maybe.
Hmm.
So we have science, monster, fear,
life.
I have zero clue.
No idea.
Let's go this way.
Oh, that's a lot of ingots.
It's a gold ingot.
Beautiful.
That's it.
Can I not pocket a couple extra for later so I can spend it at the refectory?
Get some nice pasta, some salad on the side.
Oh.
Oh, would you look at that?
Oh, yes, access cards.
Finally.
We now have access to the other two mines.
Beautiful.
Okay.
Nice.
Let's, let's slot it in.
Uh, well, I don't know where we're going, but I guess it doesn't matter.
Maybe just choose these.
Yes, beep it up.
Look at that.
Okay, but what's this all about then?
What was the point of this?
How come this one was closed?
Like, okay, this one was really weird to me.
The fact that I had to go inside of here, because I held middle mouse button, there was no prompt for this.
But I guess maybe the timer being like, dick, dick, dick, was like an indicator in my mind a little bit.
But I could easily have missed this for three hours more.
Weird.
Okay, let's head down here now.
So now we have gold and we have silver.
Actually, no, this is, yeah, this should be silver, except it doesn't have a engraving on it.
Let's just go in here.
Oh, not that one, of course.
This one.
Beep me in.
Uh, go in.
Come on, in.
There we go.
Hello?
Who spoke?
Oh, oh my God, you're stuck.
You, okay, I got greetings wrong.
You help me?
I'm sorry, I'll help you.
There you go.
Then he walks off.
Oh, what do we got here?
Yes, there it is.
There it is.
We can now make fire.
Incredible.
Okay, so that has to mean help, right?
But I'm thinking, maybe it's this one?
Does this make any sense with help?
You help me?
You rescue me?
Um, you assist me?
That does not make sense with any of these.
So if it's not that one, it needs to be one of these three.
Why did I call this one create make?
I know it doesn't work here because I tried it.
Yeah, I don't know.
Oh, I wanted to rename this.
Oh, I did already, right.
Okay, um, we got the fire.
There was a staircase over here.
Down this way.
Oh,
I knew there was going to be another terminal.
Okay, warriors don't something.
That means warrior.
Warrior.
Oh, that's the other one.
Unreadable plants.
Oh, devotees plant plants.
Right.
That has to mean devotee.
Man, we got them all now.
Warriors don't play music.
What do the warriors not do?
No, they don't.
Um, I don't know.
They don't do science.
Warriors.
Oh, I get it.
I thought this was the unreadable part that confused me a little bit.
There's something missing here.
So this means don't or not.
Not.
Right.
That makes sense.
Something plants unreadable.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Look at this.
There's like a little outline of a glyph.
Okay.
That is that one.
No, it's not.
It's not.
It's not a light.
It is.
Oh, maybe we don't have that glyph.
Is this another one of those situations where they show a glyph that I actually don't possess, but it's still part of the language.
I think so.
So it has these two lines going through in the center there.
And we know it's one of those that go around.
Similar to these ones, right?
So it's like an action.
It's a verb.
What other glyphs do we have with lines going like this one?
Carbon.
There's a couple options here.
Devotees.
Hmm.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Unreadable.
Plants unreadable.
So this means plants, of course.
What am I doing?
Plant.
Yeah.
I thought it meant planting something.
Like a flower.
You know, planting a flower.
I was confused.
But that's not what it means.
These are just plants.
Warriors don't.
Yeah.
Okay.
This one we got now.
Plants.
Oh, plants could be similar to nature.
I have a feeling it may be what needs to go in here.
Nature and plants, right?
God, I don't know.
So I have one, two, three, four, five, six left.
But I don't have many options here, which of course means that we still have things to find that we haven't found yet.
I just want to keep exploring.
Oh, nice.
That feels good.
Okay, good.
We're closing in here.
This one is still kind of annoying.
This one I'm very unsure of, actually.
I mean, I'm sure it needs to be here, but I don't know what it means.
Okay.
Let's engage the Zoom terminal.
Also, I'm the one powering it.
That power is emanating from me when they come on.
Not sure that matters, but... Okay, so alchemists are communicating with the bards.
Or technically, these are the slaves, actually.
Brothers I'm seeking.
Ooh, brothers, huh?
I think I had a word for that.
Somewhere.
It's not these.
Alchemists.
Copper.
Bard.
Brother.
I'm seeking brothers.
I.
Me.
Abba, wait.
I'm seeking brothers.
Brothers is plural.
So, right.
So, me.
Seek.
That one I have.
There.
Me seek.
Brothers.
Plural, which is that one.
Yes.
The warriors are not brothers.
I mean, that's because you don't make music.
Or maybe you're not happy with the warriors, and you would rather be friends with the alchemists, huh?
Um, okay.
The warriors are not brothers.
So, we need to do warrior.
Plural.
Not brothers.
And plural.
There we go.
Okay, and now you're saying, I found a book.
You did, huh?
Okay.
I.
Oh, I don't remember which one of these is I.
You.
It's one of those things where they go through the middle.
So, that one.
I.
Find.
Oh, god.
Seek.
What?
No.
Not quite the same, is it?
Find.
Book.
I don't remember if we even had a word for book here.
We must have.
Oh, god.
Where is it?
Oh, we do.
Okay.
Huh?
Oh, it's the reverse order, of course.
I'm a dumbass.
It's book I found.
Damn it.
Book.
I.
Found.
There we go.
Okay, now.
We are brothers.
Really?
You found that in the book?
Does the book reveal your, like, the origin of your species or something?
Share a common ancestor?
Something like that?
I mean, they probably do.
They're all humans.
So.
Evolution.
Right?
Ties into the image we have of the caterpillar and the butterfly.
Oh, that could mean brothers.
I don't know.
We already tied that into the book.
So, never mind.
You could say the caterpillar and the butterfly are brothers, right?
A brother fly.
Okay.
We are brothers.
So, brothers, we are.
Brother.
Oh, god.
I don't know what that is.
It's gotta be one of the... Nope.
Nope.
It's gotta be...
Oh, man.
Monster.
Man, human.
I'm looking for the ones that look like these.
Like, I have no idea.
Where the hell is it?
All right.
I'm going through everyone.
There it is.
This makes no sense.
This should be a glyph that looks like these.
I mean, these, where they go through the line at the bottom.
You know?
Like, warrior.
Brother.
It's a person.
Maybe that's just me.
We are brothers.
Okay.
So, brother.
We are.
So, that would be...
uh... me.
Plural.
R or to be.
Boom.
Nice.
We are brothers.
Holy shit, you're right.
We are.
I can see it in your eyes.
Or through your glasses.
We are brothers.
Where's we?
Me.
Uh, brothers.
Yeah.
Look at that.
The connection has been established.
Something has changed in the tower.
So, the slaves of the bards are now friends or brothers with the alchemists.
Very cool.
We just need one more connection.
That one.
And this one.
Actually, there's two more.
Huh.
I think I can do them right now, actually.
But I may wait until I have every single one of the glyphs in this language first.
Very cool.
Back up.
I know where to go now.
We have the fire.
Easy peasy time.
Okay.
So, from here we are going to go up here.
We need one more ingot as well.
Yeah, I hit all the way up.
Because we had a mine up here.
If I'm not mistaken.
Oh, actually, no, no.
We had fairy gate and library up here.
I'm missing something.
I have gold and I have silver.
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, I was about to say this is carbon-based life forms.
But we already used carbon.
Damn.
I don't know what it could be.
What could it be?
I don't understand.
There's not many options.
This makes no sense.
I must have gotten one of these extremely wrong.
Like this... could this mean life?
Life is made up of elements, right?
It's made of carbon.
It's made of some metals.
There's all kinds of stuff in life.
Is that what they're all getting at here?
Hey, we alchemists.
You know, we all originate from star stuff.
The stars out there in the universe are the true brothers that made us.
You know, and that involves butterflies too and caterpillars and warriors, bards, devotees, everyone.
The table that I'm sitting at is made of the same stuff.
As you and I.
I honestly think... Oh, look at that.
Art and science come together.
It's beautiful.
Maybe they teach the alchemists to play some music now as well.
Nice.
Oh, is that how they came up here?
Wait, wait a minute.
A gondola.
Oh, my God.
You just know that the alchemists made this.
You know, it's a little bit shoddy design here.
Actually, it's made of metal.
I thought it was wood.
I thought they hastily put this together.
No, no, no.
These guys are pros.
Yeah, alchemists are hanging out here among the bards.
The bards are hanging out with the alchemists.
That's cool.
Okay, I want to go back, actually.
Maybe there's more to see here.
We can check that later.
I am itching to get that last ingot.
Ingot of carbon or whatever.
Uh, and I think I know how to get it.
So we got silver, we got gold.
Oh, wait a minute.
What am I doing?
I'm being stupid right now.
Hold on a minute.
Wait a sec.
Hold on.
Gold, silver, copper.
Why the fuck was I under the imagination that we needed carbon ingots?
Because of course that makes no sense.
I forgot we had four in total.
You know, we have the metals and we have carbon.
Oh my god.
Okay, well, we got the we got these two.
Now we need copper.
So we got to go back down here.
Yeah, that's how we're going to get that.
Take me down.
This solves so many problems I had in my head.
Very nice.
Oh, this way.
No, no, no, no, no, wait, wait, wait.
We are here.
We need to take the elevator over here.
The one that is closed apparently, right?
Oh, I could have just teleported by the terminal.
Because there's a terminal down here.
Ah, but we have an issue down here.
There's monsters, which is why they closed the elevator, right?
We need to get the fire first.
Shit.
Back up.
Goddammit.
Well, at least I know what to do now.
I get it.
We're not going to be able to traverse down there without having the lantern.
The way to do this is to go up here.
We got to go through the laps.
Ah, we don't actually... No, we just take this immediately.
Because we got to go up right to here.
And then we head to the right.
Yeah.
And I wonder what I'm going to be finding in this place over here.
Wait.
Oh my God.
I'm lost again.
Shit.
Let me see the map.
I wish I had the map in my book.
Show me that map.
Oh, it was down here.
Oh, I suck.
Get back down.
I think if that map hadn't been there, I would have been better in this area.
I think the map only served to confuse me.
Oh my God.
Head to the laps.
Because it was lap three, right?
Wait.
Over here.
This way.
Up here.
No, down here, down here, down here.
This was lap two.
This is the one.
Lap three.
I bet you that's going to connect to downstairs somehow.
Okay, here we go.
Here we go.
Combine the shit.
Boom.
Not with that.
With this place.
Beautiful.
Very nice.
Ooh.
Okay.
Create.
Fire.
Help.
Yep.
We only hit... Okay.
So I guess I was right.
This means life.
It has to mean life.
Or life or nature.
Nature consists of all the elements, right?
Yep.
Yep, yep, yep.
I can't wait to see what it says.
Ha!
Okay.
Transformation.
Okay, I can see that.
I can see that.
That makes sense as well.
Yeah, because that's what life is.
You know?
It is actually just a transformation.
Evolution.
We go from one state to another.
As well as everything else in the universe.
It's just a bunch of state changes.
Okay.
Let's go inside.
Laboratory three.
Oh god, what happened in laboratory three?
Evil experiments.
Of transformation.
Oh god.
A password.
Really?
Wait a sec.
Is this it?
This is... Let me see if I remember.
5,309.
5,300.
And nine.
Wrong.
Hmm.
Okay.
Did I have some other note regarding that stuff?
Am I misremembering actually?
5,039.
Is that not nine?
It is.
Is that not five?
And this is three.
Maybe the other way.
Do we need to click a button to confirm my input?
Laboratory three.
Laboratory it says here, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Laboratory.
Maybe it's simply three or five, three, nine.
Without the zero?
Five, three, nine.
Ha!
That's weird.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Am I not remembering this right?
I need to go back to the calculator.
Maybe I'm actually misremembering everything.
Wasn't it base ten?
Let me see here.
So if I go 5,000...
Oh, wait a sec, actually.
5,300.
And nine.
Oh, 5,039.
Of course.
5,039.
Right?
Oh, did I just... I think I just put the zero in the wrong spot, actually.
I did mean 5,039.
Maybe I said it wrong.
Let's see again.
5,039.
Five?
Oh yeah, I think I did do it in the wrong order here.
39.
Yes!
Nice!
I'm a little bit worried though.
We found that in a hat, right?
So where did the guy go?
Oh, what happened here?
A very violent transformation happened here, which is what an explosion is.
A very quick transformation and release of energy.
I found the formula!
I found the transformation!
Oh, shit.
So that is... I forgot this one exactly, but there is 1,400...
Actually, I forgot the numbers.
Let me see.
No, no, I'm right.
1,405 times this element, and then this times that element.
Are we going to be noting this down?
Because that's very important.
Okay, good.
So we need this many gold, this many silver, and that many carbon.
Gotcha.
Formula.
Wonderful.
Cool.
Yeah, something happened in here for sure.
I don't want to jump down there!
Okay, I just look.
It's not Silent Hill, is it?
Yep, there's monsters down there.
Look at this, too.
Handprints.
Death Stranding style.
Someone started walking on their hands, and then transitioned to feet.
Very concerning.
You know what I think?
I think that those monsters were created by the alchemists.
Accidentally.
I mean, that's what this looks like, right?
An experiment gone wrong.
Trying to create life.
Trying to transform elements into creatures.
Well, okay.
Well, I guess I always have a light now, so we can head down to the lower levels and explore that mine.
No, this way.
I need to go to the copper mine.
And the best way to go there is... I guess we could take stairs from here?
That's one way to do it.
No?
Right?
Aren't there stairs over here?
There isn't.
God damn it.
Yeah.
For some reason, this map is so confusing to me.
Not the map on the wall.
Well, that one, too, but the layout of this place really messes with my mind.
I've never been good with directions.
Definitely one of my weak points.
This was the staircase down there.
Let's take that.
Or actually, it makes more sense to take the elevator here.
Wait.
Nope.
Back up.
I forgot where we were.
This is the elevator, right?
Jesus.
Well, I got the whole language.
Reading anything now should be a breeze.
As long as I can read English.
Okay.
And now, since we have the whole language, we can also translate the remaining terminals.
Let's head down here first, though.
Go.
Can I open this again?
I don't think I want to.
That way.
There's no monster here.
Wait a minute.
Where's the mine?
What about this way?
Is it in here?
It has to be.
Oh my god.
What the?
I am so lost.
Is there not supposed to be a copper mine down here?
Do I click on...
What?
I don't know.
Go back up.
Also, where are the monsters down here?
Very weird.
Let's see this.
I have no idea.
Gold, silver.
We have those.
We need copper now.
I mean, I could just try go back up to the machine.
But am I not going to be missing carbon?
Yeah, look, we don't have any carbon.
Oh, wait a minute.
Why would I expect to get carbon in the copper mine anyway?
That doesn't make any sense.
Oh my god.
Once again, I get these elements mixed up in my mind.
Let's just get up there.
It's not copper we need.
It's carbon.
Maybe we can find it in a different spot.
Okay, so now we go up.
Up here, it's going to take us to the transformation.
No, no, go back up this way.
Up here through the door.
Okay, here we are.
I forgot which element this was.
Okay, that was the right one.
Oh, wait, we already had carbon.
God damn it.
Unbelievable.
I did not remember this.
I just assumed that I needed to find carbon somewhere.
In some form or fashion, you know?
Um, okay.
Okay, so now we need 1,405 gold.
So 1,000.
These have to be the thousands.
This is hundreds.
No, wait, hold on a minute.
There's one, two, three, four, five different weights here.
Maybe this is more than five.
Ones, tens.
I don't know.
Oh, let's not forget.
These are flipped, right?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Makes sense.
I get it now.
These are actually precise weights.
So we need that, we need that, and we need that.
Okay.
So the first thing we need is this.
Oh, no, this.
Then we need that.
No, that.
And what was the last one?
Five.
That one.
And that was for gold.
Was that gold?
The circular one?
Yep.
Gold.
Nice.
Very good.
And then we needed this much of silver.
Okay, so that one and those two.
Got it.
That one and... Oh, but whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
This one is, I believe, eight.
Let's see.
Eight, eight, eight, eight, eight.
Where are you?
Oh, yes.
But it's like weirdly changed.
It's eight.
We don't have an eight here, so we have to combine.
And these ones are...
Let's see here.
These are the hundreds.
Eight.
We have five.
Six, seven, and eight.
Isn't that way too much, though?
Am I crazy?
That seems like a lot.
Well, in any case, we are going to need...
Oh, we also have two down here, of course, which is the ones.
Okay.
How am I going to get that?
Wait a minute.
How am I going to do that?
So we can only work with...
Actually, maybe it's better if we just think of it as a normal addition, because we only have these to work with, right?
We got to combine them.
So the thing I'm looking for is...
What is that?
812, right?
So we just have to combine it to make 812.
Yeah.
But I also want to go back to the Zoom terminals, now that I know the whole language.
I'm going to stop it here.
Thanks for watching.
I'll see you in the next.